Scott Crowley

Student of Computer Engineering

Profile

I'm a senior in the Electrical & Computer Engineering program and excited to graduate December 2021. My research and interests include control systems, embedded devices, and SoC design. I have extensive experience providing quality customer service in various fields from information technology to laboratory science to heavy machinery. I believe in taking pride in my work and ensuring my team can depend on me to help us succeed.

Education

Computer Engineering

University of Utah, GPA 3.33

2017 - Present

Associate of Science in Engineering

Great Basin College, GPA 3.75

2010 - 2017

Graduated Magna cum Laude & Dean's List.

Experience

Service Desk Agent

University of Utah Hospitals & Clinics

7/2017 - 8/2019

Providing medical staff and patients with front-line technical support to assist in resolving incidents promptly.

Laboratory Technician III

Wheeler Machinery Company

5/2014 - 7/2017

Analyzing fluid samples for customer equipment monitoring. Interpreting data and making service recommendations. Defining and maintaining standard operating procedures.

Awards

Phi Beta Kappa

Academic Honor Society

Demos

Spanish Fork, UT 801.558.7578 scott@utah.edu linkedin.com/in/ScottUT

Skills

Circuit Design

Customer Service

Data Entry & Analysis

Problem Solving

Programming

Tools

C / C++

Electronics Lab Tools

Java / C#

MATLAB

MS Excel

Python

Verilog

Visual Studio